Finding aid to the Classes of 1911-1920 records CA.MS.01018
Smith College Archives
- Class of 1920 Records, 1916-1965; 13.833 linear feet (19 containers)
  The Class of 1920 Records contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1920, including materials from commencement, reunions, senior dramatics, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, and other memorabilia.
  - Commencement, 1920 (Box 1928, Folder 1)
  - Commencement Music, 1920 (Box 1928, Folder 2)
  - Commencement Photographs, 1920 (Box 1928, Folder 3)
  - Freshman Frolic, 1916 (Box 1928, Folder 4)
  - Freshman Handbook, 1916-1917 (Box 1928, Folder 5)
  - Groups, 1916-1920 (Box 1928, Folder 6)
  - Hoop Rolling, 1920 (Box 1928, Folder 7)
  - Junior Prom, 1919 (Box 1928, Folder 8)
  - Junior Ushers, 1919 (Box 1928, Folder 9)
  - Ivy Day, 1920 (Box 1928, Folder 10)
  - Ivy Day Photographs, 1920 (Box 1928, Folder 11)
  - Last Sing, 1920 (Box 1928, Folder 12)
  - Class Letters, 1949-1976 (Box 1928, Folder 13)
  - Memorials, 1935-1960 (Box 1928, Folder 14)
  - Organization, 1916 (Box 1928, Folder 15)
  - Reunions, undated (Box 1928, Folder 16)
  - Reunions, 1923-1925 (Box 1928, Folder 17)
  - Reunions, 1930 (Box 1928, Folder 18)
  - Reunions, 1935 (Box 1928, Folder 19)
  - Reunions, 1940-1945 (Box 1928, Folder 20)
  - Reunions, 1950-1955 (Box 1928, Folder 21)
  - Reunions, 1960-1965 (Box 1928, Folder 22)
  - Reunions, 1970-1975 (Box 1929, Folder 1)
  - Reunions, 1980-1985 (Box 1929, Folder 2)
  - Reunions Songs, undated (Box 1929, Folder 3)
  - Senior Dramatics, 1920 (Box 1929, Folder 4)
  - Senior Dramatics-Photographs, 1920 (Box 1929, Folder 5)
  - Sophomore Reception, 1918 (Box 1929, Folder 6)
  - Step Sings, 1920 (Box 1929, Folder 7)
  - Songs, undated (Box 1929, Folder 8)
  - Class Supper, 1920 (Box 1929, Folder 9)
  - Class Secretary's Records (Box 1929.2)
  - Class Secretary's Records- Deceased A-H (Box 1929.3)
  - Class Secretary's Records- Deceased K-Q (Box 1929.4)
  - Class Secretary's Records- Deceased R-Z (Box 1929.5)
  - Reunion Memorabilia (Box 1929.6)
  - Individuals A-L (Box 1930)
  - Individuals M-O (Box 1931)
  - Individuals P-Z (Box 1932)
  - Adair, Edith (scrapbook) (Box 1936.8)
  - Asher, Katherine Idalia (scrapbook) (Box 1936.7)
  - Bryan, Katharine Adaline (scrapbook) (Box 1936.7)
  - Cass, Helen Landon (correspondence) (Box 1933)
  - Hill, Marian Synyer (memorabilia book) (Box 1936.6)
  - Holloway, Jeanette Rule (memorabilia book) (Box 1936.5)
  - Lawrence, Olive Ellen (memorabilia book) (Box 1936.6, Box 1936.7)
  - Macduffie, Elsbeth (memorabilia books) (Box 1936.3)
  - Macduffie, Elsbeth (scrapbook) (Box 1936.2)
  - MacDuffie, Beth, post grad (A - Z) (Box 1934)
  - MacDuffie, Beth, post grad (Writings A - O) (Box 1935)
  - MacDuffie, Beth, post grad (Writings P-Z) (Box 1936)